Pelarus, Novopolotsk
 +37529 815 05 22
 artyom.pavlyuchenko@outlook.com

Summary

Born and raised in Novopolotsk, Belarus. I graduated in machinery engineering in 2011. Between 2011 and 2021, I worked in the energy industry. I have been studying manual testing and improving my skills since late 2021.

I am open-minded and self-motivation person. I want to start a career as a junior QA engineer at the firm and in two years grow up to mid QA. Likewise, I am not ready to relocate, and I want to work remotely from my quiet place for family reasons.

Work Experience

Junior QA Engineer

2022-05 - current time

Practice on Vadim Ksendzov's course "Software Testing"

Practical training on the course in progress now. (https://github.com/APavlyuchenko)

Already used:

- Linux Terminal (using cd, ls -la, touch, mkdir, mv, rm, grep, tail commands)
- · Postman (checking status code, request and response parsing)
- Android Studio (building, running and testing the ToDoList application on a simulator and a real device)
- SQL (using select, where, like, inner join)
- JavaScript (basic concepts)

Junior QA Engineer (Trainee)

2022-01 - 2022-03

A1QA Training center, Minsk

Projects:

- **1. Information-analytical system of medical institution** (web application for checking the quality of medical staff work for 3 types of users),
- 2. Albany Aqua Ducks (web application for creating sea tours and charter flights for 4 types of users, payment info)
- 3. Gregory Olsen Photostudio (website is a business card of photographer Gregory Olsen with sections Demo, Sessions, Connect, Bio&Press and payment.),
- **4. Voyage database** (web application for creating excursions for various students and teachers, including back-end and front-end sides),
- 5. Café "Offline" menu (web application for ordering various dishes online for a week, calculating the cost, debiting from the balance),
- 6. Calculator (simple application for calculating the logarithm and square root)
- Documentation of software defects using a bug tracking system.
- Performing functional testing of projects
- Performing non-functional testing of projects (GUI, Usability, Security, Localization).
- Creating documentation for testing (Check List, Acceptance Sheet, Test Survey).
- Preparation of a Quality Report after testing.
- English language training with a campaign teacher.
- Participation in daily meetings, team buildings etc.

Welding master 2011 - 2021

Thermal power station, Novopolotsk

Area of Expertise

Operation Systems and Platforms Windows. Android, IOS

 Databases
 SQL

 Bug Tracking System
 Jira

English Pre-Intermediate

 Other
 Oracle Virtual Box, Chrome Dev Tools, Brackets, Charles

Education

Engineer 2006 - 2011

Polotsk State University, Novopolotsk

Soft Skills

- Strong analytical skills
- Comfortable with multitasking
- Long term Software QA career minded
- Positive attitude

Hobbies

• Table tennis • Pilates • Motorcircles • Training gym

Achievements